Finding Aid for the Daniel C. Prince Papers and S.T.A.R. Collection
Special Collections Manuscripts and Rare Books
- Environments
  - Greco, John - Holyland USA - Final Report, September 1984 (Box 20, File 13)
  - Greco, John - Holyland USA - Publications (Box 20, File 14)
  - Greco, John - Holyland USA - Outgoing Correspondence (Box 20, File 15)
  - Greco, John - Holyland USA - Incoming Correspondence (Box 20, File 16)
  - Greco, John - Holyland USA - Clippings (Box 20, File 17)
  - Greco, John - Holyland USA - Clippings (Box 20, File 18)
  - Greco, John - Holyland USA - Clippings (Box 20, File 19)
  - Greco, John - Holyland USA - Committee to Save John Greco’s Holyland (Box 20, File 20)
  - Greco, John - Holyland USA - Cavin-Morris Inc, Exhibit (Box 20, File 21)
  - Greco, John - Holyland USA - Information on State Register of Historic Places (Box 20, File 22)
- Environments
  - Gupton, Tyree - Heidelburg Project (Box 21, File 1)
  - Hampton, John - Throne of the Third Heaven (Box 21, File 2)
  - Hupeden, Ernest - Painted Forest (Box 21, File 3)
  - Knight, Leonard - Salvation Mountain (Box 21, File 4)
  - St. EOM (Edward Owens Martin)- Land of Pasaquan (Box 21, File 5)
  - McKissack, Jeff - The Orange Show (Box 21, File 6)
  - Prisbrey, Tressa - Bottle Village (Box 21, File 7)
  - Rodia, Simon - Watts Towers (Box 21, File 8)
  - Smith, Fred - Wisconsin Concrete Park (Box 21, File 9)
  - Tawana, Kea - Ark (Box 21, File 10)
  - Verdirome, Sal - Sanctuary of Love (Box 21, File 11)
  - Wickham, Enoch Tanner - Buckminster Hollow Sculptures (Box 21, File 12)
  - Wickham, Enoch Tanner —Exhibit Catalog Drafts 1-3 (Box 21, File 13)
  - Wickham, Enoch Tanner —Exhibit Catalog Draft 4, Final Edits, Printed Version (Box 21, File 14)
  - Wickham, Enoch Tanner —Exhibit Materials (Box 21, File 15)
  - Woitko, Joseph (Box 21, File 16)
  - Zoettl, Joseph —Ave Maria Grotto (Box 21, File 17)
  - The Dreambuilders Exhibit - John Turner (Box 21, File 18)
  - Grassroots Art: Past, Present, and Future (Symposium at Jersey City Museum) (Box 21, File 19)
  - Kansas Grasssroots Art Association (Box 21, File 20)
  - SPACES - Saving and Preserving Arts and Cultural Environments (Box 21, File 21)
  - Assorted Materials (Box 21, File 22)
  - Assorted Clippings (Box 21, File 23)
- Business
  - Business-Assorted Lists and Notes (Box 22, File 1)
  - Business -Assorted Lists and Notes (Box 22, File 2)
  - Business- Clippings (Box 22, File 3)
  - Business, Employees- Prospective Resumes, Interns and Others (Box 22, File 4)
  - Business - Exhibit Sites (Box 22, File 5)
  - Business, Financial—Accounting (Box 22, File 6)
  - Business, Financial—Cornerstone Bank (Box 22, File 7)
  - Business, Foundations --A-C (Box 22, File 8)
  - Business, Foundations --D-G (Box 22, File 9)
  - Business, Foundations --H-J (Box 22, File 10)
  - Business, Foundations --K-P (Box 22, File 11)
  - Business, Foundations --Q-Z (Box 22, File 12)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants - General Information (Box 22, File 13)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants—California, General (Box 22, File 14)
- Business
  - Business, Foundations and Grants—California, California Arts Council Artist in Residence (Box 23, File 1)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants—California, City of Los Angles Cultural Affairs Department (Box 23, File 2)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants—Connecticut, General (Box 23, File 3)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants—Connecticut, State of Connecticut Commission on the Arts (Box 23, File 4)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants—Georgia Trust for Historic Preservation (Box 23, File 5)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants—NEA (National Endowment for the Arts) (Box 23, File 6)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants—Non-Profit Resources/ Grantseekers Horizon Newsletter (Box 23, File 7)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants—Tennessee, General (Box 23, File 8)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants—Tennessee, Allied Arts of Greater Chattanooga (Box 23, File 9)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants - Tennessee, Association for Visual Artists (Box 23, File 10)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants—Tennessee, Disabilities (Box 23, File 11)
  - Business, Foundations and Grants—U. S. Artist Survey Proposal (Box 23, File 12)
  - Business, Insurance—Exhibit Coverage Materials (Box 23, File 13)
  - Business, Insurance—Lampe-Batkin Associates Inc., Policies, 7 Nov 1988-28 Mar 1994 (Box 23, File 14)
  - Business, Insurance—Lampe-Batkin Associates Inc., Policies, 10 May 1995 - 24 Jun 1997 (Box 23, File 15)
  - Business, Insurance—Lampe-Batkin Associates Inc., Account Statements (Box 23, File 16)
  - Business, Insurance—Taylor-Lawlor Agency Inc., Policies (Box 23, File 17)
- Business
  - Business, Insurance—Taylor-Lawlor Agency Inc., Account Statement (Box 24, File 1)
  - Business—Internal Revenue Service, Employee Identification Number (Box 24, File 2)
  - Business—Internal Revenue Service Materials (Box 24, File 3)
  - Business, Inventory—Artworks at Loft, photos (Box 24, File 4)
  - Business, Inventory - Assorted (Box 24, File 5)
  - Business, Inventory—Assorted lists (Box 24, File 6)
  - Business, Inventory—Connecticut Inventory, Loft, August 1995 (Box 24, File 7)
  - Business, Inventory—Damage Inventory, 1994 (Box 24, File 8)
  - Business, Inventory - Earthquake Damage Materials (Box 24, File 9)
  - Business, Inventory—Inventory Lists from 7/23/90, plus Addendum (Box 24, File 10)
  - Business, Inventory—Los Angles Inventory, January 1995 (Box 24, File 11)
  - Business, Inventory—McCarthy, Justin (Box 24, File 12)
  - Business, Inventory—Nashville, Inventory, January 1995 (Box 24, File 13)
  - Business, Inventory, January 1995 (Box 24, File 14)
  - Business, Inventory—Sales in, 1990 (Box 24, File 15)
  - Business, Inventory—Sales in, 1993 (Box 24, File 16)
  - Business, Inventory - Assorted Incomplete Inventories (Box 24, File 17)
  - Business, Lease - North Carolina Lease (Box 24, File 18)
  - Business - Magazine Contacts (Box 24, File 19)
  - Business - Museum Contacts (Box 24, File 20)
  - Business - Photographer Contacts (Box 24, File 21)
  - Business, Price Lists—Assorted (Box 24, File 22)
  - Business, Price Lists—Assorted (Box 24, File 23)
  - Business, Prince Art Consultants - Film and Television Contracts (Box 24, File 24)
  - Business, Prince Art Consultants - Henshey’s Building Materials (Box 24, File 25)
  - Business, Prince Art Consultants - Heyman Properties (Box 24, File 26)
  - Business, Prince Art Consultants - Original Design Work for Advertisements, Letterhead, and Business Cards (Box 24, File 27)
  - Business, Prince Art Consultants - Publicity Materials (Box 24, File 28)
  - Business, Prince Art Consultants - Receipts and Cancelled Checks (Box 24, File 29)
  - Business, Prince Art Consultants - Representative Agreements (Box 24, File 30)
  - Business, Prince Art Consultants—Sale Proposals for Patrons (Box 24, File 31)
  - Business, Prince Art Consultants - Statement of Purpose and General Materials (Box 24, File 32)
  - Business—State of California, Board of Equalization (Box 24, File 33)
- Business
  - Business—State of California, City of Santa Monica Business License (Box 25, File 1)
  - Business—State of Connecticut, Department of Revenue Services (Box 25, File 2)
  - Business—State of Georgia, Business License and Department of Revenue (Box 25, File 3)
  - Business—State of New York, Business Certificate (Box 25, File 4)
  - Business, To Do Lists - Assorted (Box 25, File 5)
  - Business, To Do Lists -Labeled, Assorted (Box 25, File 6)
  - Business, To Do Lists -Letters, Assorted (Box 25, File 7)
  - Business, To Do Lists - Phone lists and Addresses, Assorted (Box 25, File 8)
  - Business, To Do Lists - Schedules and Dated Lists, Assorted (Box 25, File 9)
  - Business, To Do Lists - Schedules and Dated Lists, Notebooks (Box 25, File 10)
  - Business, To Do Lists - Schedules and Dated Lists, Notebooks (Box 25, File 11)
  - Business, To Do Lists - Schedules and Dated Lists, Notebooks (Box 25, File 12)
  - Business, To Do Lists -Dan’s Datebooks, 1981, 1986, 1987 (Box 25, File 13)
  - Business, To Do Lists -Dan’s Datebooks, 1988, Jul-Dec. 1989, 1991, 1992 (Box 25, File 14)
  - Business, To Do Lists -Dan’s Datebooks with Addresses and Phone Numbers (Box 25, File 15)
  - Business, To Do Lists -Dan’s Datebooks with Addresses (photocopies) (Box 25, File 16)
  - Business, To Do Lists - Dan’s Datebooks w/ Addresses (photocopies) (Box 25, File 17)
- Business
  - Business, To Do Lists—Dan’s Datebooks w/ Addresses (photocopies) (Box 26, File 1)
  - Business, To Do Lists—Dan’s Datebooks w/ Addresses (photocopies) (Box 26, File 2)
  - Business, To Do Lists—Misc. Business Cards—Artists, Art Organizations & Patrons for contact (Box 26, File 3)
- STAR
  - STAR, Artist Call—House of Blues Proposed Site (Box 26, File 4)
  - STAR, Artist Call—San Diego, CA. (Box 26, File 5)
  - STAR, Artist Call—San Francisco, CA., Fort Mason (Box 26, File 6)
  - STAR, Artist Call—Stanford, Connecticut (Box 26, File 7)
  - STAR, Artist Survey—Art Across America (Box 26, File 8)
  - STAR, Newsletter—Vol. 1 #1 (Box 26, File 9)
  - STAR, Newsletter—Vol. 1 #2 (Box 26, File 10)
  - STAR, Newsletter—Vol. 1 #3 (Box 26, File 11)
  - STAR, Newsletter—Vol. 2 #1 (Box 26, File 12)
  - STAR, Newsletter—Vol. III # 1 (Box 26, File 13)
  - STAR, Newsletter - Vol. IV Winter, 1999 (Box 26, File 14)
  - STAR, Non-Profit Status—Correspondence (Box 26, File 15)
  - STAR, Non-Profit Status—Internal Revenue Service 501(c)(3) Forms (Box 26, File 16)
  - STAR, Non-Profit Status—Internal Revenue Service 501(c)(3) Application (Box 26, File 17)
- STAR
  - STAR, Non-Profit Status—Internal Revenue Service 501(c)(3) Application Support (Box 27, File 1)
  - STAR, Non-Profit Status—Internal Revenue Service 501(c)(3) Application Support (Box 27, File 2)
  - STAR, Non-Profit Status—Internal Revenue Service 501(c)(3) Letter Granting Status (Box 27, File 3)
  - STAR, Non-Profit Status—Internal Revenue Service 501(c)(3) Draft Support (Box 27, File 4)
  - STAR, Non-Profit Status—State of California, Application Materials (FTB 3500) (Box 27, File 5)
  - STAR, Non-Profit Status—State of California, Application Declined (FTB 3500) (Box 27, File 6)
  - STAR, Non-Profit Status—State of California, Certification of Articles of Incorporation (Box 27, File 7)
  - STAR, Non-Profit Status—State of California, Statement of Domestic Nonprofit Certification (Box 27, File 8)
  - STAR, Projects—Outlook Nashville, 2002 (Box 27, File 9)
  - STAR, Projects—Youth Villages (Box 27, File 10)
  - STAR—Proposals (Box 27, File 11)
  - STAR—Vanderbilt University (Box 27, File 12)
  - STAR—Vanderbilt Archives—Assorted Materials (Box 27, File 13)
- Patron Files
  - Apfelbaum, Ben (Box 28, File 1)
  - Arient, Jim (Box 28, File 2)
  - Arnett, Bill (Box 28, File 3)
  - Bahm, Darwin (Box 28, File 4)
  - Barashkoff, Sophia (Box 28, File 5)
  - Barrett, Didi (Box 28, File 6)
  - Baumgarten, Heidi and Rovins, Andy (Box 28, File 7)
  - Becker, Scott and Jennifer (Box 28, File 8)
  - Belding, Bill (Box 28, File 9)
  - Bell, Stu (Box 28, File 10)
  - Benson, Ray (Box 28, File 11)
  - Berkeley, Jim (Box 28, File 12)
  - Bishop, Robert (Box 28, File 13)
  - Botwin, Will (Box 28, File 14)
  - Bowen, Diane (Box 28, File 15)
  - Brady, Susan (Box 28, File 16)
  - Brezzo, Steve (San Diego Museum of Art) (Box 28, File 17)
  - Broad, Eli (Box 28, File 18)
  - Brown, Lynne (Box 28, File 19)
  - Bunnen, Lucinda (Box 28, File 20)
  - Burnett, Ruth (Box 28, File 21)
  - Burruss, Tim and, Mary (Box 28, File 22)
  - Caldwell, Ben (Box 28, File 23)
  - Carlos, Ann (Box 28, File 24)
  - Cartin, Mickey (Box 28, File 25)
  - Chouinard, Roger and Mariko (Box 28, File 26)
  - Coleman, Dick (Box 28, File 27)
  - Cohn, Barbara (Box 28, File 28)
  - Comsky, Dave (Box 28, File 29)
  - Conkelton, Sheryl (Box 28, File 30)
  - Costello, Phil (Box 28, File 31)
  - Cowden, Brian (Box 28, File 32)
  - Datene, Ludwig and Meta (Box 28, File 33)
  - Davis, Francesca (Box 28, File 34)
  - DeWitt, Don and Marian (Box 28, File 35)
  - Doonan, Kathleen (Doonan Designs) (Box 28, File 36)
  - Erlich, Steve (Box 28, File 37)
  - Emley, Joseph (Box 28, File 38)
  - Emsden, Maya (Box 28, File 39)
  - Epheren, Jerry (Box 28, File 40)
  - Fagot, Chris (Box 28, File 41)
  - Fagot, Lucy and John (Box 28, File 42)
  - Farrell, Susan (Box 28, File 43)
  - Ferreira, Ann (Box 28, File 44)
  - Finkelstein, Alan (Box 28, File 45)
  - Finkelstein, Bill (Box 28, File 46)
  - Fogle, Glen (Box 28, File 47)
  - Friedman, Estelle (Box 28, File 48)
  - Fritz, Ken and Fritz, Brenda (Box 28, File 49)
  - Fyuvlent, Robert (Box 28, File 50)
  - Gehry, Frank (Box 28, File 51)
  - Gelber, Lisa (Box 28, File 52)
  - Gersh, Gary and Maria (Box 28, File 53)
  - Gitter, Kurt and Yellin, Alice (New Orleans Museum of Art) (Box 28, File 54)
  - Gold, Jeff (Box 28, File 55)
  - Goldstein, Marci (Box 28, File 56)
  - Griffith, Christa (Box 28, File 57)
  - Grossman, Bonnie (Box 28, File 58)
  - Grossman, L. Jay (Box 28, File 59)
  - Guest, Naomee (Box 28, File 60)
- Patron Files
  - Haardt, Anton (Box 29, File 1)
  - Hahn, Marshall (Box 29, File 2)
  - Hall, Julie and Michael (Box 29, File 3)
  - Harmon, Mark (Box 29, File 4)
  - Harte, Wendy and Rob (Box 29, File 5)
  - Hartigan, Lynda (National Museum of American Art) (Box 29, File 6)
  - Heller, Liz (Box 29, File 7)
  - Hemphill, Bert (Box 29, File 8)
  - Heyman, Samuel (Box 29, File 9)
  - Hiatt, John (Box 29, File 10)
  - Hicks, Robert (Box 29, File 11)
  - Holland, Edward (Box 29, File 12)
  - Hood, John (Box 29, File 13)
  - Hudson, Holly (Box 29, File 14)
  - Hunecke, Bert (Box 29, File 15)
  - Hunsinger, Joann (Box 29, File 16)
  - James, Everett H. (Box 29, File 17)
  - Jamsheed, Juliet (Box 29, File 18)
  - Johnson, Christine (Box 29, File 19)
  - Jones, Jerilyn (Box 29, File 20)
  - Karelson, Mark (Box 29, File 21)
  - Keats, Steven (Box 29, File 22)
  - Kellaway, Tom (Box 29, File 23)
  - Kelley, Harmon and Harriet (Box 29, File 24)
  - Kinberg, Robert (Box 29, File 25)
  - Kind, Phyllis (Box 29, File 26)
  - Klein, Michael (Box 29, File 27)
  - Kline, Sandra (Box 29, File 28)
  - Koenig, Robert (Box 29, File 29)
  - Kogan, Lee (Museum of American Folk Art) (Box 29, File 30)
  - Kreisler, Les and Ellen (Box 29, File 31)
  - Krittenden, Carol (House of Blues) (Box 29, File 32)
  - Kuheenschmidt, Richard (Box 29, File 33)
  - Lee, Spike (Box 29, File 34)
  - Levinson, Barry and Diana (Box 29, File 35)
  - Liefeld, Rob (Box 29, File 36)
  - Lyons, Joan (Box 29, File 37)
  - Mainwaring, Mark (Box 29, File 38)
  - Margeas, Bob (Box 29, File 39)
- Patron Files
  - McInnes, Ellia (Pawlovsky) and Robert (Box 30, File 1)
  - Meister, Michael (Box 30, File 2)
  - Mendelsohn, Gael and Michael (Box 30, File 3)
  - Messer, Sam and Gauers, Eleanor (Box 30, File 4)
  - Meyer, Don (Box 30, File 5)
  - Mull, Martin and Mull Wendy (Box 30, File 6)
  - Murphy, Tony (Box 30, File 7)
  - Norton, Peter and Eileen (Box 30, File 8)
  - O’Keefe (Box 30, File 9)
  - Packer, Aaron (Box 30, File 10)
  - Patashnik, Stephen M. (Box 30, File 11)
  - Pawlovsky, Jim (Box 30, File 12)
  - Perry, Michael (Box 30, File 13)
  - Pfeiffer, Bob (Box 30, File 14)
  - Philbin, Peter (Box 30, File 15)
  - Pike, Martha (Box 30, File 16)
  - Post, Karen (Box 30, File 17)
  - Preston, Aubrey (Box 30, File 18)
  - Prince, Jim (Box 30, File 19)
  - Ramis, Anne (Box 30, File 20)
  - Rand, David (Box 30, File 21)
  - Reder, Milton (Box 30, File 22)
  - Rosenack, Jan and Chuck (Box 30, File 23)
  - Rosenthal, Richard (Box 30, File 24)
  - Ross, Paul and Fein, Judith (Box 30, File 25)
  - Rothman, David (Box 30, File 26)
  - Saks, Eric (Box 30, File 27)
  - Santos, Karina (Box 30, File 28)
  - Sawyer, Sue (Box 30, File 29)
  - Schmidt, Duane and Dianne (Box 30, File 30)
  - Schuss, Kerry (Box 30, File 31)
  - Schwartz (Box 30, File 32)
  - Seaton, Esta (Box 30, File 33)
  - Shear, Alex (Box 30, File 34)
  - Shulman, Tom (Box 30, File 35)
  - Siegel, Randy (Box 30, File 36)
  - Sims, Frank (Box 30, File 37)
  - Skinner, Robert W. (Box 30, File 38)
  - Stern, Jane and Michael (Box 30, File 39)
  - Stein, John and Kim (Box 30, File 40)
  - Steiner, Neil and Smith, Susan (Box 30, File 41)
  - Stipe, Michael (Box 30, File 42)
  - Strouser, Sterling (Box 30, File 43)
  - Summers, Andrew (Box 30, File 44)
  - Sween, Barry (Box 30, File 45)
  - Thaon, Olivier (Box 30, File 46)
  - Thompson, Mike (Box 30, File 47)
  - Tolle, Charles D. (Box 30, File 48)
  - Trocki, Phillip (Box 30, File 49)
  - Urban, Hope (Box 30, File 50)
  - VanDerElst, G. H. (Box 30, File 51)
  - Vinetz, Tom (Box 30, File 52)
  - Walker, Michael (Box 30, File 53)
  - Wallace, Matt and Ranstrom, Melodie (Box 30, File 54)
  - Walsh, Klune (Box 30, File 55)
  - Warner, Linda (Box 30, File 56)
  - Weisman, Frederick R. (Box 30, File 57)
  - Weitzer, Steve (Box 30, File 58)
  - West, Ruth (Box 30, File 59)
  - Williamson, Bernard (Box 30, File 60)
  - Wilson, Langford (Box 30, File 61)
  - Wilson, Timothy (Box 30, File 62)
  - Wolf, Jonathan (Box 30, File 63)
  - Wolfe, Townsend (Box 30, File 64)
  - Wood, Bill (Box 30, File 65)
  - Zala, Nancy (Box 30, File 66)
  - Zetter, Lois (Box 30, File 67)
  - Scouting on prospective patrons (Box 30, File 68)
  - General (Box 30, File 69)
- Correspondence
  - Outgoing, 1976-1992 (Box 31, File 1)
  - Outgoing, 1193-1994 (Box 31, File 2)
  - Outgoing, 1995-2000 (Box 31, File 3)
  - Outgoing—A-M, undated (Box 31, File 4)
  - Outgoing—N-Z, undated (Box 31, File 5)
  - Outgoing—Fagot, Mary (Box 31, File 6)
  - Outgoing—First Names Only, A-K (Box 31, File 7)
  - Outgoing—First Names Only, L-W (Box 31, File 8)
  - Outgoing—Form Letters (Box 31, File 9)
  - Outgoing—Miscellaneous (Box 31, File 10)
  - Incoming—Anderson, Brooke -Art Write (Box 31, File 11)
  - Incoming—Babroff, Jerilynn - Bishop, Robert (Box 31, File 12)
  - Incoming—Blume, Anna - Byrne, David (Box 31, File 13)
  - Incoming—Caldwll, Willa - Crichton, Don (Box 31, File 14)
  - Incoming—Dandanell, Mary – Durham, Laura Elizabeth (Box 31, File 15)
  - Incoming—Ehrlich, Susan and Ehrlich, Martin (Box 31, File 16)
  - Incoming—Fagot, Mary (Box 31, File 17)
- Correspondence
  - Incoming—Fagot, Mary - Fonville, Sandra (Box 32, File 1)
  - Incoming—Gagnon, Steve - Green Helen (Box 32, File 2)
  - Incoming—Hall-Duncan, Nancy - Hyatt, Eric (Box 32, File 3)
  - Incoming—Ingram, Lynne - Jesudowich, Stanley (Box 32, File 4)
  - Incoming—Kaplan, Carol - Knowles, Susan (Box 32, File 5)
  - Incoming—Laffal, Flo - Luck, Barbara (Box 32, File 6)
  - Incoming—Malone, James - Moses, Kathy (Box 32, File 7)
  - Incoming—Nakian, Paul - Northway, Heather (Box 32, File 8)
  - Incoming—Oberberger, Christine - Owen, Carla (Box 32, File 9)
  - Incoming—P. John - Perrish, Laurence (Box 32, File 10)
  - Incoming—Pizer, Bradley - Prince, Phyllis (Box 32, File 11)
  - Incoming—Racht, Judith - Rohrer, Tina (Box 32, File 12)
  - Incoming—Roush, Mike - Ruzicka, Paul (Box 32, File 13)
  - Incoming—Samuelson, Pam - Shear, Alex (Box 32, File 14)
  - Incoming—Sheedy, Ally - Subtle, Susan (Box 32, File 15)
  - Incoming—Thompson, Jim - Tomlin, Wendell (Box 32, File 16)
  - Incoming—U-V (Box 32, File 17)
- Correspondence
  - Incoming—Welser, George – Zlyima ?, Lily (Box 33, File 1)
  - Incoming—Unidentified A – M (Box 33, File 2)
  - Incoming—Unidentified P – T (Box 33, File 3)
  - Incoming—Unidentified (Box 33, File 4)
  - Incoming—Unidentified (Box 33, File 5)
- Organizations & Events
  - Auctions, Art Fairs, and Antique Malls (Box 34, File 6)
  - Bayside District Corporation (Santa Monica, Ca.) (Box 34, File 7)
  - Burning Man Festival (Box 34, File 8)
  - Café 458 (Box 34, File 9)
  - Creative Growth (Box 34, File 10)
  - Creativity Explored of San Francisco (Box 34, File 11)
  - Exceptional Children’s Foundation (Box 34, File 12)
- Organizations & Events
  - Exhibits - Assorted (Box 34, File 1)
  - Exhibits – A Good Likeness, General Materials (Artists, Sales, Business) (Box 34, File 2)
  - Exhibits – A Good Likeness, Catalogue (Box 34, File 3)
  - Exhibits – A Good Likeness, Curatorial Materials (Box 34, File 4)
  - Exhibits – A Good Likeness, Lecture Notes (Box 34, File 5)
  - Exhibits – A Good Likeness, Lecture Mailing List, Guest List and Invitation (Box 34, File 6)
  - Exhibits – A Good Likeness, Public Relations Materials (Box 34, File 7)
  - Exhibits – A Good Likeness, TULA Guest list (Box 34, File 8)
  - Exhibits – A Hand Has Five Fingers, Santa Monica Place, Curatorial Materials (Box 34, File 9)
  - Exhibits – A Hand Has Five Fingers, Santa Monica Place, Press Contacts (Box 34, File 10)
  - Exhibits – A Hand Has Five Fingers, Santa Monica Place, Letters to Press (Box 34, File 11)
  - Exhibits – A Hand Has Five Fingers, Assorted Materials (Box 34, File 12)
  - Exhibits – Art’N Park, Spring, 1994 (Box 34, File 13)
  - Exhibits – Biggest, Assorted Materials (Box 34, File 14)
  - Exhibits – Biggest, Blank Forms, Signage, Press Releases (Box 34, File 15)
  - Exhibits – Biggest, Catalogue Drafts (Box 34, File 16)
  - Exhibits – Biggest, Catalogue Excerpts (Box 34, File 17)
  - Exhibits – Biggest, Copyright Materials (Box 34, File 18)
  - Exhibits – Biggest, Correspondence (Box 34, File 19)
- Organizations & Events
  - Exhibits – Biggest, Guest Book and Catalogue Sign-up (Box 35, File 1)
  - Exhibits – Biggest, Original price Lists (Box 35, File 2)
  - Exhibits – Biggest, Working Papers (Box 35, File 3)
  - Exhibits – California Discoveries (Box 35, File 4)
  - Exhibits – California Discoveries (Box 35, File 5)
  - Exhibits – “Contemporary Folk Art: A view from the Outside” (Box 35, File 6)
  - Exhibits – Familiar Territory (Box 35, File 7)
  - Exhibits – 50 Flavors of Flight (Box 35, File 8)
  - Exhibits – Fighting Windmills: An Exhibit of Environmental Art with C.E.T.A. Housing Authority (Box 35, File 9)
  - Exhibits – Flight of Fancy (Box 35, File 10)
  - Exhibits -- Labels (Box 35, File 11)
  - Exhibits – Lyndon House Show (Box 35, File 12)
- Organizations & Events
  - Exhibits - “Made to Last; Metal work in America” (Box 36, File 1)
  - Exhibits - “Made to Last; Metal work in America”, Rough Draft Exhibition Catalogue (Box 36, File 2)
  - Exhibits - “Made to Last; Metal work in America”, Loan Forms (Box 36, File 3)
  - Exhibits - Outsider Art Inside (Box 36, File 4)
  - Exhibits - Passing in the Outsider Lane (Box 36, File 5)
  - Exhibits - Passing in the Outsider Lane, Tennessee State Museum (Box 36, File 6)
  - Exhibits - Rebuilding Liberty: Old and New Themes in American Folk Art (Box 36, File 7)
  - Exhibits - Rebuilding Liberty, Text and Photocopies (Box 36, File 8)
  - Exhibits - The Self-Taught Artist: A Celebration of African-American Folk Art (Box 36, File 9)
  - Exhibits - Silvermine Guild Arts Center, Outsider Art Exhibit with Larry Armistead and John Jordan (Box 36, File 10)
  - Exhibits - Strong Enough, Vanderbilt University Medical Center (Box 36, File 11)
  - Exhibits - University Club of Nashville, May 1998 (Box 36, File 12)
  - Exhibits - Untitled Exhibition Layouts (Box 36, File 13)
  - Exhibits - “We Built It Ourselves: AN Exploration of Folk Environments Across the United States” (Box 36, File 14)
  - Exhibits - Working Hard: The Art of John Jordan (Box 36, File 15)
  - Exhibits - Fall Antiques Show at the Pier, 1985, 1986, 1991 (Box 36, File 16)
  - Organizations & Events - First Street Gallery Art Center (Box 36, File 17)
  - Organizations & Events - Florida Folklife Programs (Box 36, File 18)
- Organizations & Events
  - Organizations & Events – Free Arts For Abused Children (Box 37, File 1)
  - Organizations & Events – Folk Art Society of America, General Information (Box 37, File 2)
  - Organizations & Events – Folk Fest, The World’s Greatest Folk Art Show and Sale, 2000 (Box 37, File 3)
  - Organizations & Events – Galerie atelier Herenplaats (Box 37, File 4)